heyy guys so it's in January in 2025 and
I'm here in benel Mad a Costa to show
you this Resort option uh this is
located here on the cadell Saul area of
Spain in the south of Spain right on the
south coast directly opposite
Morocco so there's lots of different
Resorts up and down the coast but I'm
going to focus the tour today on benel
Mader and tell you the reasons why you
want to come to benel madna tell you
much information as possible about benel
madna and just show show you all the
prominade and show you the beach and
show you some cafes bars restaurants and
give you information about the prices
and how to get here as
well so the first thing you'll notice is
the Porto Marina which is just be just
just up these steps here on the left
side there's a really really beautiful
boat marina with all the yachts and the
boats and it's full of restaurants very
very good quality restaurants in in Asia
is my favorite restaurant there on that
Marina it is absolutely fantastic
they've got every type of food you have
you pay one price and you can eat
whatever you want there's another
restaurant called W restaurant that I
recommend there on the Porto marinaa uh
very very good restaurant as well and it
has all very good Asian food you can eat
as much as you want within the price
of20 um and there's lots of cafes up and
down the prom here
too so so the bus stop is um up these
steps you go left and you just go up
that hill for about 3 minutes and the
bus stop is there to take you up up and
down the coast to all the different
Resorts if you want to try out some
neighboring Resorts just maybe get the
bus from there um as you can see there's
some lovely cafes and everybody's
enjoying the sun
today so this one the Terrace is full of
people hello
hello so this is the typical Ambiance
here of Beno mtin
Costa and the sign there just below the
trees it's decorated in lovely colors
and that says benel Madina over there as
well I really really like benel mad it's
a lovely place for a holiday and you can
come here the whole year around because
it's got over 320 days of Sun every
single year here in uh benom
madna so look at these wonderful tall
palm trees here just straight ahead I'll
just focus in a bit closer for
you and you can see the walkway there
the benom Mad
sign behind the benom Mad sign you've
got the uh the Porto Marina there and
it's worth having a walk around by the
Yachts there on the front of the marina
uh you've also got prison Island there
on the top floor you've got a
supermarket an El cot and glaz
Supermarket there so if you want a
supermarket that's one of the best
supermarkets basically we have Marks and
Spencers they have ELC Eng and uh it's a
super core it says super core outside
which is the name of the supermarket but
it's owned by elor
in in terms of prices mercadona
Supermarket is actually cheaper than AL
C for just your basic things like eggs
and water and that type of thing and
vegetables but elot is very very high
quality um the focus is on quality so
you've got the beach there in the
background and uh it's a big wide Beach
stretching all down the coast right down
the coast there uh in the midle you can
see where they play beach volleyball in
the
summertime today is about 18° in sunny
again it's been 18° every day for the
last four or 5 days the weather has just
been lovely this
January and this is why this is a very
good place for winter sun as well
because it has a really good all year
round
climate you'll find there's lots of
cafes here with sun traps uh my hotel I
stay in the Don Pedro Hotel um part of
the S Hotel Group it's part of the s
Resort in Tor Molinos and they have the
sa Don Pabo Pablo hotel and the Saul Don
Marco Hotel as well so the three there's
a selection of eight pools there's uh an
indoor pool there's hot tubs there's
saas so even if it is raining you can
just use the facilities in your hotel if
you stay in the right hotel but if you
don't stay in a hotel with a gym like
mine has a really good gym in the hotel
you can see straight ahead just in the
center there there is a free gym for
people there on the prominade so maybe
you're staying in some basic
accommodation and uh you can just go
down use the gym there on the
prom so this is the start of the walkway
uh you can see the they call it the Paso
maritimo in Spanish
language and it stretches all the way
down so benl madna has three different
sections you've got benl mad Costa which
is here this is the prominade of benel
mad a Costa and it's going to stretch
down for about 1 mile down the path I'm
walking you down now uh you have um you
have aryo deel which is the Inland part
of benom Madina and that is where benel
mad train station is located so if
you're getting the train from the
airport there is no stop that says benel
mad I must warn you you get off at aryo
deel and that is where you get off and
then you walk down the hill because
that's up at the top of the hill in a
Royo deel it's a beautiful town it's
very very Spanish you see all the
tradition tap pass bars and everything
else you will really really like it in
aroyo De La especially if you want to
try some Spanish food and some
tapas so you can see all the families
there walking along the
prom so today from T Molinos to here
it's taken me about 40 minutes walk I
walked on the way from you you go from
Tor Molinos through a resort called La
carella where all the people from
Holland stay lots of people from the
Netherlands stay there it's a very very
beautiful fishing Village and Resort and
um it's very lowrise La carella very
very good for shopping lovely lovely
cafes and it's very very picturesque as
well so I do recommend a visit for to
Lac arella as well if you stay in B on
mner it is worth the
walk getting from the airport it's about
20 minutes in a taxi from Malaga AGP
airport where you fly to to get here to
benom Mad a
Costa all the train will cost you about
€3 to get €3 to get from the airport to
um to a Royo de out on the
train so you'll find that there's a wide
variety of restaurants up and down here
they all have boards outside with
different promotions always have a look
and see if there is a menu Del
menu Del DEA is the menu of the day
where you get three course meal for
about 13 or 15 uh you'll get a starter
and a main course and a dessert for that
price and that's like a special
promotion between 12:00 and 4:00 Monday
to Friday menu
Dela so let's have a look at the menu
see the prices guys it's always good
idea to get a an idea of the prices
before you come here so a coffee or a
tea is €130 very very very cheap indeed
and a coffee and Brandy is €250 it's
good value for money in this
one in La carella it was like double the
price to be honest of this this one here
and um a half pint is
€130 was in a bar yesterday in ferola
and I paid €180 so it's h it's actually
cheaper than ferola down here in this
particular one and a bottle of wine for
€750 that's about £6 very very good
value for
money Sam Miguel half liter is €3 so
that's for a pint of San Miguel Spanish
beer toasty of the day
€390 special hot baguette with fries and
salad $550 or a hamburger is €7 which is
about
£550 omelette with fries and salad
that's €7 very very good deal well it's
very busy in this place cuz um prices
are very reasonable
[Music]
well in the winter a lot of retired
people come out here just to hang out
for the winter time they can only stay
now for a maximum of 3 months after the
brexit now unfortunately Britain's left
the European Union so I'm really
disappointed about that but um our time
is now restricted to 3 months every 6
months to spend here in Spain in the Sun
so um be aware that you you can't go
over your 90 days and now there are
limitations on the amount of tobacco and
the amount of alcohol you're allowed to
bring back home now you're only allowed
to bring 200 Cigarettes back to Britain
with you and now you're only allowed to
bring one bottle of wine or um or one
bottle of spirits back with you because
we're no longer part of the European
Union this has caused a very very big
problem on the coast because a lot of
British people were living here and
they've had to move they've had to move
back
[Music]
home it's caused huge difficulties the
brexit in terms of paperwork and
everything else with the Brits that were
living here they've had to go to the
immigration office over and over again
to sort out all their paperwork it's
caused an absolute mess this brexit
because there was a massive massive
British population living here on the
cadell so a lot of people make a joke
and they were calling it Britain in the
son for many years I used to live down
here as well and it was full of expats
from Britain Ireland Scandinavia Holland
Germany from so many different countries
Austria oh what city in Austria are you
from near inbook um salsburg I went to
Vienna last year ah VI it's on on East
and we are West oh Old Mountain skiing
and so skiing yeah is it nice there for
a holiday thank you bye bye yeah so
there's people here from so many
different countries around the world
here and that's why it's a wonderful
place for a holiday here and the cadel
Sal here is famous for golf the whole
Coast is full of golf courses especially
in in marbo which is a bit further down
the coast that is the home of golf here
uh there are so many good golf courses
if you're a
golfer in terms of winter tourism uh a
lot of the tourists here tend to be
retired people that are coming over here
um in my hotel there's also a lot of
families that are on holiday there
they've come away from Nordic countries
where it's very very cold for winter sun
I live in Poland in kov at the moment
and in kov it's very very cold it's like
min-1 -2° right now so you just need
these Winter Sun Holidays just to get
you to get you your Vitamin D and to get
you keep you going through the winter if
you live in a place like
that so I also re commend you the sea
life center which is on the benom madna
marina if you want to go to the sea life
center with your children and your
family they will really really enjoy
seeing all the different types of fish
species there in the sea sea life center
I recommend you download an application
called
groupon. and then you get discounts from
that application in places like the sea
life center and on Prison Island and
that type of thing all the entertainment
things for children
so here in terms of shopping there's
lots of different options you can see
straight ahead here's um a clothes store
here straight ahead and uh they've got
all types of women's clothing there as
well uh there's the musician going by
there they have musicians all up and
down the coast every single day all
different types of music yesterday in
Tor Molinos town I saw a jazz show and
um later in the day I went down to
ferola to ferola Market and I recomend
you f Rand Market is on Tuesday every
single week um you get it off at the
fairground bus stop so what you can do
is either get the bus from T Molinos or
from MAA or from wherever you stay up to
the fairground bus stop in uh Los biches
area of ferola and they have a big
massive market and this Market is
absolutely wonderful you can buy the
bags the polo t-shirts you can buy the
shorts the tracksuits you can buy the
watches you can just buy everything all
the copies I was buying Polo T-shirts
there four four polo t-shirts were
€45 all the names Ralph luren Gant um
Armani you know all the names that you
want you know when you need some extra
t-shirts when you're away on holiday and
you can just buy all the copies there so
um I do recommend for wola
Market just to show you how lovely it is
really
those lovely
trees and let's turn the camera and get
you a lovely view of the
[Music]
coast so guys in terms of hotels uh I
recommend you stay in uh the hotel Don
Pedro really really good hotel to stay
in the millia hotel is also a very very
good hotel to stay in in t Molinos as
well and um here in Ben madna there's
also plenty of options of places to stay
in here but not quite the same quality
as those two hotels um millia hotels are
very very high quality and S hotels are
very very high quality they have all the
entertainment in the evening all the
live music and everything in these
hotels
[Music]
so in terms of buying Sun cream in these
places here um Sun cream is very very
expensive when you buy it here in the
resort it will be 50% cheaper at least
when you buy your sun cream in England
go to shops like Savers and super drug
in England and you'll buy your sun creen
very very cheaply just a money saving
tip for you there as
well when you're buying counter feat
products and copies like the gentleman
Straight Ahead from senagal the lucky
lucky men make sure you negotiate
they'll start with a very high price
like €200 for a watch you must negotiate
very very carefully and offer them a
lower price for the product that you
want and uh offer them a low very low
price at first and then you'll come to
an agreement to buy the product that you
[Music]
want so you get people up and down the
coast the guys here from Sagal from
Africa selling all different types of
copies and products um bags and t-shirts
and tracksuits and watches so you can
buy everything you want when you're on
holiday um they're copies but they look
quite similar to the real
ones in terms of buying a small beer
most of these places are about €2 for a
small beer some of them are €150 for a
small
beer and you can see the price of the
creps here let me just have a look so
the creps are €4 in this one here all
one is $545 a CP with ice cream
inside and they do the juice here and
the juice is
€3 just so you can
see often they have a board outside
displaying promotions and prices it's
really nice have a look at the prices
before you go in uh make sure you're
comfortable with those prices you go in
before you go in let me have a look show
you some prices on here
uh the prices vary from place to place
so one place might be a very very good
deal uh if it's busy it's normally a
good deal this one's quite busy and if
it's very quiet it's probably an
expensive
[Music]
one so these are the types of bags you
can buy Here Eve San Lon
Gucci
Prada some of the ladies bags there
[Music]
hello mate any watches
today watch relock
reloc do you have to watch have to watch
yeah hublo HBL yes a director oh
director okay thank you mate where are
you from where fromal Sagal nice one I'm
from Liverpool
you have money money yeah
s yeah but I'm Everton but I'm from
Liverpool cheers man thank you byebye
byebye so the guys down here they're all
from Sagal so they love football and um
I'm actually from Liverpool in England
uh but I'm a fan of Everton the the blue
football team in
Liverpool a lot of the senle all these
guys here they're actually fans of
Liverpool cuz Liverpool pool had lots of
sagales players over the years so that's
the reason
why so here it goes down onto the beach
let me just show you and here's the uh
chiringos so a chiringo is basically a
beach bar so Spanish people they talk
about chewing gitos a lot they like to
go to beach bars that are directly on
the
beach in terms of a glass of wine here
you're paying about €3 for a glass of
wine in most of these places but in the
supermarket for about €4 you can buy
full bottle of wine um I do recommend
the wine is very very high quality it's
made here in Spain I recommend that you
bring some wine back to England with you
maybe bring a couple of bottles back for
your
friends guys if you've got any comments
as well to recommend things to see and
do here in b madna or on the Costa Del
Sol please make some comments cuz it
does tell help the tourists that are
coming over here on holiday and please
give likes as well on my channel cuz it
does help it does help the video go high
if you give it likes and if you can
please subscribe to my Channel at travel
with call with a c and then you'll see
all of my guided tours from Spain and
from many many other
countries let me just take you down here
now and I'll show you what it's like in
the chering gito today on a
Tuesday it's about 3:00 in the afternoon
right now it must have gone up to about
20 or 22° right
now here we
go what a lovely place to
sit the air is so fresh very very good
here for
wellness and straight across the sea
here on a clear day you can see Morocco
it's well worth going for a day trip to
Morocco as well guys um on the ferry
that will take you through to
Tangier and Tangier is one of the best
cities in Morocco and that is a a
special place where you can buy all the
copies you can buy all the counter feet
copies like armanii Gucci Nike Adidas so
you get all your copies over there and
the Spanish just fill their bags and
come back to Spain with all the copies
that they bought over in
Morocco it's going to take you about 45
minutes from tarfa on the ferry to get
to Morocco on the catamaran but um you
need to get a bus from here to tarfa and
that's going to take you probably about
3 hours hours in total or 2 and 1 half
hours and then the catamarans run on a
regular basis going across to Morocco um
that will take you 45 minutes on the
fast one but if you get the ferry from
alerz the regular one from alerz then
that's a bit slower and I think that
takes 3 or 4 hours to get over to
Morocco depending on which one that you
get but it is a bit cheaper if you get
the slow one as well so that's something
to bear in mind I also recommend you a
day trip down to jalter jalter is a
taxfree zone so um you can buy bu your
cigarettes and your alcohol very very
cheaply in jalter jalter is like a
British
colony um it's on a big rock on a big
mountain there and you can see the
monkeys there in jalter as well so
that's quite unusual for a day trip but
um you only need a day trip to jalter
you can see everything there in one
day so as you get further down the coast
down here you hit the other Resorts um
so you're going in the direction of
pangara which is the next big Resort
they have a wonderful Marina in ferola
called the Porto depoto which means the
Sports Port and it's full of restaurants
and bars and you can look at the Yachts
there on ferola
Marina after ferola you carry on down
the coast and you get to a few other
small Resorts like Kalah Honda and
cabopino and then you reach Mara Mara is
one of the most luxurious resorts on the
coast Mara is a really really beautiful
Resort I used to live in Maya before I
moved to Poland and it's a lovely lovely
place
but you've got different areas of Mara
you've got Mara Oldtown which is very
traditional Spanish with whitewashed
andalucian streets beautiful flower
baskets all around the old town and it's
just absolutely beautiful and then
you've got areas of my like PTO and in
PTO B all the most famous people in the
world live there in PTO B that's like
the California of Europe it's very very
high ends beautiful yacht sports cars
Lamborghinis Ferraris if you want to
meet famous people go down there to
Porto
news so guys thank you very much for
watching my guided tour today and I hope
it helped you with some of my tips
anyway and please subscribe to my
YouTube channel at travel with call and
that's call with a c cheers guys thank
you very much bye-bye