[Music]
did you know that estona often dubbed
The Garden of the cadel Soul boasts over
20 km of Coastline and a Charming Old
Town adorned with vibrant flower pots
imagine strolling through picturesque
streets lounging on pristine beaches and
indulging in authentic Andalusian
Cuisine all in one place welcome to
estap pona a Hidden Gem on Spain's
southern coast that offers a perfect
blend of relaxation and adventure in
this video we're presenting the big
local estapa travel guide from mustsee
attractions to Insider tips we've got
everything you need to make your
estepona trip
Unforgettable so let's dive into the
Wonders that await you in this Coastal
Paradise
[Music]
estona is situated on the Costa Del
Saul in the province of Malaga Andalusia
southern Spain nestled between the
Mediterranean Sea and the Sierra Bera
mountains it offers a unique blend of
coastal and mountainous
Landscapes the town covers an area of
137 s km and enjoys a microclimate with
over 325 days of sunshine per year
making it a year-round
destination traveling to estepona is
straightforward the town is
approximately 80 kilm Southwest of
Malaga the provincial
capital if you're driving from Malaga
take the aova A7 Coastal Highway and
you'll reach estapa in about an hour
depending on traffic alternatively the
ap7 toll road offers a faster route with
less congestion for international
Travelers Malaga airport is the nearest
major airport offering flights to and
from numerous Global
destinations from the airport you can
rent a car take a bus or arrange for a
shuttle service to
estona if you're planning a onewe road
trip why not spend it along the stunning
Andalusian Coast check out our video
explore Andalusian Coast in 7 days for
the ultimate Seaside Adventure hidden
beaches Charming coastal towns and
breathtaking views await watch it after
this estapa is just the
beginning start your journey in eston's
Oldtown a maze of narrow whitewashed
streets adorned with colorful flower
pots each Street boasts its own unique
color scheme creating a vibrant and
picturesque
setting don't miss the Plaza deas floors
a Charming Square filled with cafes and
the perfect spot to people
watch looking for the perfect Beach day
pad Del Cristo is a family-friendly Cove
with calm shallow Waters and soft sand
it's an ideal spot for swimming
sunbathing or enjoying a picnic plus
with two beach bars cheering guidos on
site you can Savor local seafood without
leaving the shore for those seeking
Tranquility this beach offers a peace
environment surrounded by natural
vegetation despite its Serene setting
it's equipped with amenities like
showers and public
restrooms nearby Sonora Beach Club
provides a spot to socialize enjoy live
music and Savor local
Cuisine for a wild adventure visit selo
Aventura a safari park home to over
2,000 animals in semi- Wild conditions
from Lions to giraff
this park offers an African safari
experience right in estapa it's a hit
with families and animal lovers
alike art enthusiasts will appreciate
the root of artistic murals where large-
scale artworks Adorn building facades
throughout the town this open air
Gallery adds a creative flare to
estepona streets and is a testament to
the town's commitment to art and culture
eston's seafront prominade is a favorite
among locals for leisurely strolls
jogging and enjoying sea views the
well-maintained path is lined with palm
trees Gardens and offers access to
various beaches in chying guidos beach
bars this Botanical Park in orchidarium
houses over 3,000 plant species
including approximately 1,500 orchid
species it's a Serene spot where locals
and visitors alike can appreciate
diverse flora and the architectural
beauty of the glass do
structure estepona boasts a variety of
eateries cherished by residents offering
everything from fresh seafood to
traditional and illusion
flavors nestled in the marina this
beloved Seafood spot is a go-to for
locals craving The freshcious Catch of
the Day the laidback No Frills setting
enhances the experience allowing the
Flav to take Center Stage signature
dishes include grilled octopus garlic
prawns and the house favorite fried
anchovies pair your meal with a crisp
glass of local white wine while enjoying
views of the bustling por Las
ganas tucked away in eston's Charming
Old Town this intimate restaurant is a
Hidden Gem for Andalusian Cuisine with
its whitewashed walls rustic wooden
beams and flower filled patio the
Ambiance transports d miners to a
traditional Spanish home the menu
highlights include slow cooked oxtail
Iberian pork and locally sourced Seafood
all crafted with a focus on quality
ingredients and time-honored
recipes El Patio Del macarina a classic
tapas bar loved for its warm hospitality
and authentic Regional flavors located
in a pictures Courtyard it's the perfect
spot to sample a variety of small plates
from crispy croas and jam mon bero to
sizzling gambas Salah the Lively
atmosphere often accompanied by
traditional Spanish guitar music makes
it a favorite among locals looking for
an authentic dining
experience end your day at the estapa
marina bustling with restaurants bars
and shops it's the perfect place to
enjoy fresh seafood sip on a cocktail or
simply watch the boats drift by
on Sundays the marina hosts a market
where you can shop for souvenirs and
local
crafts and there you have it your
comprehensive guide to experiencing the
best of
estona whether you're exploring the
Charming Old Town relaxing on sun-kissed
beaches or embarking on a Safari
Adventure estona offers something for
every
Traveler if this guide has inspired your
next getaway don't forget to hit the
like button and subscribe for More
Travel insights have you been to
estepona or have questions about
planning your trip leave a comment below
we'd love to hear from you