Hello, hello. Welcome to Christy's Way
again and today the vlog is about um the
Grand Marba Hotel we are staying and
let's check out the hotel
We have the champagne and the juice and
water. What would you like to have,
>> my dear husband? What would you like to
have?
>> Nada.
>> He He wants nothing. But for the
audience, I will take a champagne.
That's our nice room.
My dear husband hiding.
And that's the washroom we have. That's
also very nice.
Very, very, very nice.
And you have all the amenities we need.
Correction. There are four pools. Four
pools. Three for the adults
>> and one for the kid. And there's a fifth
pool which is in the beach club. So,
this is the third one. And behind that,
there's a baby pool. Four pools. Wow.
And the beach.
This hotel has in every corner a lot of
chill out areas and the whole rustic
architecture
and the furniture everything is just so
beautiful
and every chill out corner is is
amazing.
From the top of the hotel, you can also
see the ocean. Look at the beauty.
And not just the ocean,
you see the mountains as well.
They have a super cool gym and lot of
activities. So, tomorrow at 9 to 10
there is functional training which I
will surely go.
Good job.
>> So now we are going to the beach club.
So the hotel also has a beach club but
the beach club is outside.
Uh so that I guess it's also accessible
then to everybody to come. So let's go
and check out the beach club. What I
understood is that the beach club is
still being renovated. So some part of
the beach club is finished and some not.
The part that is not finished is the spa
and sauna which we will really miss. So
minus one for that. But when that's
ready, I think this would be a very nice
place to come. So let's go.
Here
is the Amu Beach Club and the Sham
Pine Health Spa. Anyways, help us health
spa is not ready. Let's go to the beach
club.
So, the main activity in the Grand Mava
Resort is um actually going to the pool,
looking at the beach, going to the pool
and lying down like that.
And the good thing is that it's not
really overcrowded though. The hotel is
really big. We see very less people.
Maybe it's because it's too big that you
don't get to see people. Uh I think we
might see all of them for breakfast
tomorrow.
There's a pigeon who's drinking water
from our pool. Hello
This is the breakfast place also. Very
nice. You can also sit inside and
outside if you wish.
And they have buffet as well as alakat.
And I would obviously go for my ex
benedict as usual.
So that was my vlog about the Grand
Marba Resort and Beach Club. Uh we
really like this place. It's very
relaxing and the whole architecture very
rustic.
um very maybe I don't know what not to
say. It's beautiful. So if you like this
vlog, please do like, share and
subscribe. And if you're coming to Mara,
this is surely a good option for you to
come check it out.